broadcast tonight or a private battle blows wide open in public has the most powerful Republican in Washington
今晚播出或私人的战斗打击敞开的公共拥有最强大的共和党在华盛顿
Sassy's how to not be coming out swinging against members of his own party
野蛮女友的怎么不来反对他自己的党的成员摆动
execution big news on North Korea tonight with young leader has taken out of family member
今晚执行对朝鲜的大新闻与年轻的领导人已经采取了家庭成员的
too close for comfort the case of the interpreter at Mandela memorial has gone from embarrassing questions about security in a big breast
太近舒适解释在纪念曼德拉的情况下，已经从尴尬的问题有关安全的一大乳房
breast cancer walk in the cut the Redskins have
乳腺癌走在切是红人队
for some women with far fewer side effects to deal with
对于一些女性少得多副作用处理
making a difference for US sailors far from home
使得美国水兵远离家乡有差别
nightly news begins
晚间新闻开始
New York NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams leaving today
纽约NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯今天离开
Washington was a rare outburst of candor mixed with anger and frustration whatever anyone thinks about the Speaker of the House John Boehner mail
华盛顿是坦率的罕见爆发的愤怒和沮丧不管有人认为对众议院博纳邮件议长混合
job in Washington his job is to lead his majority party Republicans in Congress is problem has been the rise of the Tea Party faction
在华盛顿工作他的工作就是带领他的多数党共和党在国会的问题一直是茶党一派的兴起
the newly arrived in highly motivated members who do not go along or get along with the wishes of the leadership
新近抵达充满活力的成员谁不走或相处的领导层的意愿
they force banners hand on the fiscal cliff and again in the government shut down now they've gone after a budget deal that represents real compromise and keeps the country running
他们强行对财政悬崖标语的手，又在政府关闭现在他们已经走了一个预算协议，代表真正的妥协后，保持国家运行
the speaker today decided he's had enough and he said so Kelly O'Donnell was there for on Capitol Hill today and starts off from there tonight Kelly tape
扬声器今天决定他受够了，他今天说凯利·奥唐奈在那里在国会山，并从那里开始了今晚凯利胶带
Brian the house is Justin something we haven't seen in a long while overwhelmingly passing a budget deal Democrats and Republicans intended to end the crisis de prices atmosphere we've been living with
布赖恩房子是贾斯汀的东西我们还没有看到在很长一段时间压倒性通过一项预算协议民主党人和共和党人打算结束这场危机去的价格气氛，我们一直生活
managing his own Republican membership has been taught what made harder by the influence of outside group instantly criticizes peel before it was announced
管理自己的共和党籍已教了什么外界团体的影响力做出努力瞬间批评剥离它宣布前
news conference of the year John Boehner took the little kids 17 frustrations conservative political groups
当年约翰·博纳的新闻发布会上把小的孩子17挫折保守派政治团体
join this moment being able to speak up and speak your mind in a way that we haven't seen as much
加入此时刻能够说话，说出你的想法，因为我们还没有看到尽可能多的方式
discount store Point WI nuh uh some people stop over the line when you criticize something and you have no idea what you're criticizing I eat on your mind you're going to believe
量贩店点威斯康星努赫呃一些人在停止线的时候你批评的东西，你不知道你在批评我吃的东西对你的心你要相信
speaker shipped to the Tea Party victory support Republicans in charge 3 years ago he doesn't share their political DNA is the Chamber of Commerce style Republicans firebrand
音箱运到分管茶党的胜利支持共和党3年前，他并不认同他们的政治DNA是商会风格共和党煽动者
the Tea Party headphone confrontations put his leadership on the rocks repeatedly now he has a message for the conservative groups do men did the government shutdown strategy to stop the healthcare law
茶党耳机对抗把他领导的岩石上反复现在他有做男人做了政府关闭策略，以阻止医疗保健法律的保守团体的消息
the day before the government reopen a lot of people up one of these words will never really thought would work
前一天，政府重新打开了很多人了这些话人会真的从来没有想到会工作
the fallout Swift does conservative groups to oppose today's budget deal Arnold Palmer
的后果雨燕确实保守团体反对今天的预算协议阿诺德·帕尔默
presenting the voices of the American people that are not being represented by the officials in Congress
展示了美国人民的那些不是由官员在国会代表的声音
Kansas Republican to use camp is tea party through and through is Boehner is not conservative enough
堪萨斯州共和党用营地是茶党通过和通过的博纳是不够保守
I have difficulty trusting anybody in Washington that is dismissive American people
我很难相信任何人在华盛顿说是不屑一顾的美国人民
the conservative rift over tonight budget compromise include Thomas GOP senators with the Rhone political features to consider is Marco Rubio
在今晚的预算妥协保守的裂痕包括托马斯共和党参议员与罗纳政治功能要考虑的是马可·卢比奥
as a conservative do you believe this isn't a deal you can back
作为一个保守的，你相信这不是一个交易可以备份
is a conservative American
是一个保守的美国
the biggest complaint is that this deal would spend more for the government funding over the next couple of years don't do enough they say to reduce the deficit more than 30
最大的抱怨是，这笔交易将花费更多的政府拨款，在未来几年没有做足够他们说削减赤字超过30
30 House members passes tonight expected to go to the Senate were it will also path may be putting a lid on some of the crisis mode with living with Brian
30家成员传递今晚预计要到参议院被它也会路径可以把盖子上的一些危机模式与生活与布莱恩
any bentyl and different kind of day on Capitol Hill Kelly O'Donnell there for Oliver Kelley facts word has arrived from overseas the leader of North Korea has executed a family member
任何bentyl和不同种类的一天在国会山凯利·奥唐奈那里奥利弗·凯利事实字来自海外的朝鲜领导人执行的家人赶到
Kim Jong Un has had is own on Cole killed
金正云已是自己对科尔被杀
after making a very public display of removing him from power back when his father Kim Jong Il ran North Korea this very soon
使得从电源取出他的一个非常公开展示背部时，他的父亲金正日跑到朝鲜这之后不久
uncle was considered very high ranking for Hep C the number to man in the country this execution is one way for this young new leader to show the world
叔叔被认为是非常高的排名为酷C到人在该国数这个执行是为这个年轻的新领导人向世界展示了一个办法
in very graphic terms that he is firmly in charge Archie Florida fairs correspondent Andrea Mitchell here with us in the studio tonight
在非常图形方面，他是坚决负责阿奇佛罗里达州博览会记者安德里亚·米切尔在这里与我们在今晚工作室
good evening Ryan indeed this official announcement is the clearest evidence the major shake up by this little Regina North Korea nuclear power carving alarm in Washington North Korea's most powerful neighbor China
晚上好瑞恩这的确是官方公布的是最清楚的证据，在华盛顿朝鲜最强大的邻国中国这个小里贾纳朝鲜核能雕报警器的主要动摇
Kim Jong on the young untested leader now eliminating the power behind the phone executing is ona Jung sung tech
金正日对年轻的未经考验的领导者现在省去后面执行手机电源奥纳荣格技术传唱
Bianca wouldn't believe in charge of training is young nephew to take over now according to North Korea is official announcement executed as a trader in fact called quote Despicable humans come worse than a dog
比安卡不会相信负责培训年轻的侄子接手现在根据朝鲜官方宣布签立的说法，实际上是一个贸易商报价称为人类卑鄙来比狗更差
cute animals price cursed acts of treachery in the trailer such a profound trust in one is paternal love shown by the party and the leader for him and it claims he confessed at a military tribunal what was clearly show trial
可爱的动物价格背信弃义的拖车被诅咒的行为，在这样一个深刻的信任，是党和领导人对他表示父亲的爱，并声称他在军事法庭是什么交待清楚显示试验
his downfall was shown on state TV earlier this week when he was arrested shown being pulled out of a public meeting young send text has been used as a potential economic
他的倒台是在本周早些时候表示在国家电视台的时候，他被逮捕所示拉出一个公开会议上年轻发送文本已被用来作为一个潜在的经济
former in charge of a transition of power then second in command he was also the pointment for maintaining canyons relationship with Beijing
前掌权力的过渡，然后二把手，他也是pointment维持峡谷与北京的关系
is there is no reason to doubt the official announcement of execution official fat if confirm this is another example of the brutality
是没有理由怀疑执行官方发正式公布，如果确认是残酷的另一个例子
North Korean virgin penetration is not my friend about cursing and consulting without eyes in what is now clearly a crisis on the new crisis
朝鲜处女普及率不是我的朋友关于诅咒，没有眼睛的咨询在什么是现在显然是一个危机的新危机
Victoria from over there and Rhea Texas always
维多利亚从那边瑞亚德州总是
now the latest or the latest twist in a story that as we set off the top of the broadcast started as simply an embarrassment
现在在一个故事的最新或最新的扭曲，当我们掀起了广播的顶部开始作为一个单纯的尴尬
what is now raising more serious questions about security for President Obama and the other world leaders who came to South Africa for the Mandela memorial as we were making our way back home from there the sign language interpreter who was called out as a fake
什么是现在提出有关安全总统奥巴马和谁来到南非的曼德拉纪念，因为我们是回家从那里使我们的方式，其他国家的领​​导人更严重的问题，谁被称为作为一个假的手语翻译
revealed news about himself and what he claimed what's the history of serious mental illness NBC's Ron Allen has the latest tonight from Pretoria
关于他自己和他所声称什么严重的精神病史NBC的罗恩·艾伦有最新今晚从比勒陀利亚透露的消息
today temperature going to explain is questionable content of a mental Memorial just Epps away from President Obama and other leaders medication for schizophrenia breakdown on stage
今天的温度要解释的是一种精神纪念刚刚艾普可疑内容远离奥巴马总统和其他领导人用药台上精神分裂症击穿
images you said he has a history of violence behavior
你说的影像，他有暴力行为的历史
sometimes I feel like me
有时我觉得像我这样的
stunning revelations by a man already accused of being a fraud its Friday
由已被指控为诈骗其周五男人惊艳的启示
that the individual that baby is having significant a mental issues I was allowed to stand next to the president in other countries is the amazing and very frightening
那个人说宝宝是有，我被允许旁站到其他国家的总统显著一种心理问题，是惊人的，非常可怕
portable security concerns at the Mandela memorial NBC News the Secret Service was very concerned
在曼德拉纪念NBC新闻特勤便携式安全问题非常关注
range
范围
the president security motorcade was stuck in traffic
总统车队的安全性是在堵车
screaming seems to be non existent extra strength
尖叫似乎是不存在的额外的力量
Stadium without any physical screening White House in secret service jobs under difficult circumstances obviously they
体育场没有任何物理筛分白宫特勤局的工作困难的情况下显然他们
work very hard
工作很辛苦
and that's so cold
这就是那么冷
Terrapin complaints before
龟投诉前
wake me complain
叫我抱怨
we feel that the South African government holidays
我们认为南非政府假期
Marie Curie standpoint
居里夫人的立场
the major embarrassment set something much worse 10 News Victoria
主要设置的尴尬事情变得更糟10维多利亚新闻
news tonight from the International Space Station yesterday's reported problem is not as dyrus first thought in the crew has time to consider it options including a spacewalk to fix it
今晚的新闻从国际空间站昨天的报告的问题并不像在剧组dyrus首先想到的有时间来考虑选择，包括太空行走来解决它
NASA loves redundancies they are good to have in space the Pampas broke as a working back up but still is a problem that will need attention in the meantime today
美国宇航局喜欢裁员，他们都好有空间的潘帕斯打破了作为一个工作备份，但仍然是今天需要注意在此期间的一个问题
The Crow was pretty much back to business as usual as we approach the one your mark on Saturday in the tragedy at Sandy Hook Elementary in Newtown Connecticut
乌鸦是几乎回到一切照旧当我们接近上周六一个你的商标的悲剧在桑迪胡克小学在Newtown康涅狄格
there is a plea tonight from this country psychologist they say the gun issue is not just a political issue the protecting our
还有今晚从这个国家的心理学家，他们说枪的问题不是保护只是一个政治问题认罪我们
from gun violence including their own homes is a matter instead of Public Health and so we get the story tonight from our chief medical editor Dr Nancy Snyder
从枪支暴力，包括他们自己的家是一个问题，而不是公共健康，所以我们从我们的首席医学编辑南茜·斯奈德博士拿到今晚的故事
it was nearly two years ago would like so many other times Ashland Milton drop her son know of is bestfriends house to spend the night
那是两年前想很多其他时间亚什兰米尔顿放弃她的儿子知道是bestfriends家过夜
about 115 in the morning we got a phone call
约115早上，我们接到一个电话
what went to your got you pull the pin for all that activity outside the house
怎样去你得到了你拉针为所有活动在屋外
any lab shopping before I talk to a cop like there's no way this is this is real or fake
任何实验室的购物之前，我跟一个警察像有没有办法，这是这是真的还是假的
but it wasn't a mistake
但它不是一个错误
13 year old son accidentally shot by his friend in a moment horseplay didn't realize the gun was loaded would you hold a cannibal
13岁的儿子不小心被他的朋友在一个时刻胡闹出手没意识到枪是加载，你会抱一个食人族
asparagus with caper children safe
芦笋雀跃的孩子的安全
Ashland family a gun owners and Avan hunters what they keep your guns locked insecure Underwood parents who don't do the same to be held legally responsible
亚什兰的家庭有枪业主和爱王猎人他们保持你的枪锁不安全安德伍德的父母谁不这样做将追究法律责任
Queens safe with car seat with put the belfry drive the speed limit we had cattle medicine that they can get in I just guns is right there with that
皇后与安全汽车座椅用把钟楼开车的车速限制，我们不得不牛药，他们可以在我刚拿到枪是在那里与
Tinseltown tragedy at least 173 children under the age of 12 have died from gunshots in the US according to original reporting and research by NBC News nearly half of those deaths were accidental
12岁以下的好莱坞悲剧至少173名儿童从美国枪声根据由NBC新闻原创报道和研究去世将近一半的死亡是意外
coming year is projected turnover people die from gun related to pass a number people die from motor vehicle desk
明年预计营业额从人与枪传递一些人从机动车办公桌死亡
Dr William babies in the ER the day of Newtown tragedy advocating that only to change gun laws changed the way we view gun violence
威廉博士的婴儿在急诊室的新城悲剧主张只有改变枪支法的日子改变了我们看待枪支暴力的方式
why is research important research is paramount when you have a discussion about the public health issue of gun safety
为什么研究重要的研究是最重要的，当你有任何关于枪支安全的公共卫生问题的讨论
in 1996 the gun lobby work successfully to hold the City season of gun violence what the National Rifle Association has always advocated
在1996年的枪支游说工作，成功举办枪支暴力的城市是什么季节全国步枪协会一直主张
safety education it didn't respond to a request for comment President Obama has called on Congress to provide 10 million dollars to fund gun research
安全教育并没有置评奥巴马总统的请求作出响应呼吁国会提供1000万美元枪的研究资助
catching your chest
捕捉你的胸部
Ashland Milton hope occasion and new laws my mother for pain
亚什兰米尔顿希望之际，新的法律我母亲的痛苦
I want to watch him go to high school in and graduated and get married and have kids
我想看他去高中毕业，结婚和生孩子
start a conversation with your children at home and talk to other parents for playdates for overnight after a simple question of guns
开始与孩子交谈在家和枪支后，一个简单的问题，跟其他家长一起玩通宵
House of a loaded and most important are they locked up and away from kids is a real transformation to make gun violence a public safety in public health
的加载和最重要的房子被他们锁起来，并远离孩子是一个真正的转变，使枪支暴力的公共卫生公共安全
spectrasoul bra store in NC thank you as always so I have for us tonight Big House news about preventing breast cancer in Newark
spectrasoul文胸店在数控感谢您一如既往的，所以我对我们今晚大宅门新闻关于预防乳腺癌在纽瓦克
Shin for women at high risk cups the risk in half with far side effects and later making a difference even on the flight deck of a guided missile cruiser big surprises for Americans serving far from home doing holiday
新的高危妇女杯半远的副作用，后来作出区别，甚至在飞行甲板远离家乡的服务做假期导弹巡洋舰大惊喜美国人的风险
we're back here with as we mention some good news about fighting breast cancer for women at high risk there may be a new way to prevent the disease without all the side effects of so many people have come to dread
我们又回到这里，因为我们说一下战斗乳腺癌的高危妇女有可能是一种新的方式，以防止这种疾病没有这么多的人的所有副作用一些好消息来畏惧
Anne Thompson has more tonight on the new research presented the day add a meeting of breast cancer specialists in Texas
安妮·汤普森今晚有更多的新的研究提出增加全天的乳腺癌专家在得克萨斯州会议
temperature is a competitor and a pioneer vending 23 years with Houston Astros 11 is President she's the longest serving female executive in Major League Baseball season honored in the Hall of Fame
温度是一个竞争者，一个先驱自动售货机23年，休斯顿太空人队11是总统，她的服刑时间最长的女主管在美国职棒大联盟赛季荣幸在名人堂
success is no defense against disease breast cancer runs in Gardners family putting her at higher if she's managed it with eggs and removal of Steuben online but no drugs yet
成功是对疾病乳腺癌运行在加德纳的家人把她在更高的，如果她设法用鸡蛋和去除斯托本的在线，但没有药物无人防守还
I'm where does over the last 50 years and I've elected not to take them but now there's something new that they're looking at that may be an option for me
我在那里做了近50年来，我已经决定不带他们，但现在有一些新的东西，他们正在寻找，可能是我的选择
something new is actually Rock
新的东西实际上是摇滚
anastrozole sold commercially is Arimidex has been used for years
阿那曲唑市售是瑞宁得已使用多年
postmenopausal women
绝经后妇女
after they've had breast cancer feel buy estrogen
他们已经有后乳腺癌觉得买的雌激素
now is study published today does an Astra soul can help prevent a virgin feel breast cancer in high risk women in first person controlled trials decreasing the rest by 53 percent researchers say its a homerun
现正研究今天发表并阿斯特拉的灵魂可以帮助防止处女了53％的研究人员说感觉乳腺癌高危妇女的第一人称对照试验降低，其余的一个本垒打
it works on both dimensions more effective in left side effects
它可以在两个维度更有效地左副作用
tamoxifen another drug use for prevention has major side effects
他莫昔芬另一种药物用于预防具有重大的副作用
tamoxifen harms are increased risk of uterine cancer blood clots Cataracs little so hot flashes
他莫昔芬的危害会增加子宫癌的血块Cataracs一点，以便潮热风险
studying bald almost 3900 postmenopausal women between the ages of 40 and 72 were increased risk for breast cancer
研究几乎秃3900 40和72岁之间的绝经后妇女增加患乳腺癌的风险
how got an ass result everyday others got a placebo after me in 5 years 40 women on an Astra soldat breast cancer vs 85 on the placebo group so who could this help women with the family history of breast cancer does with dense breasts
如何得到一屁股结果每天别人之后我在5年内40名妇女在阿斯特拉Soldat的乳癌比85在安慰剂组有一个安慰剂所以谁可以这样帮助妇女患乳腺癌的家族史确实有密集的乳房
add note to have some type something on lock
添加注释不会对锁定某种类型的东西
building a second career as a consultant the struggle for Gardner a new way to stay in the game
建设第二事业作为顾问的斗争加德纳一种新的方式留在游戏中
Ann Thompson NBC News New York
安·汤普森NBC新闻纽约
back in the moment with a little boy on a mission a lot of other Americans might like
早在上一个任务有一个小男孩当下很多其他美国人可能会喜欢
does who ate her the story that the new head of the FCC wants to allow cell phones on planes while in the air is not as bad as you might have first fear
没有谁吃了她，在FCC的新掌门人希望允许手机在飞机上，而在空气不那么糟糕，因为你可能有第一次恐惧的故事
it's all about allowing people to use their devices to text and web surfer not to make calls in fact a bill is introduced in the Senate today
它是所有关于让人们使用他们的设备今天的文字和网页浏览者不作其实是一个法案在参议院呼吁出台
what prohibits cell phone
什么禁止手机
Asians on commercial flights Golden Globe nominations are out and as usual there some surprises and some snubs leading the way with 7 nominations of peace are the films 12 years a slave in American hustle
东方人对商业航班金球奖提名都出来了，像往常一样有一些惊喜，有些怠慢一路领先以7项提名和平是电影12年从美国喧嚣
the film the butler got shut out of the major category so did homeland on Showtime HBO lead the way with 90 min Asians Wall many expect the big prize to go to breaking bad
管家得到拒之门外的主要类别电影如此做的祖国在Showtime HBO带路90分钟亚洲华尔街许多人预计的大奖去破坏
polar and Fey host a game this year at eros January 12 on NBC
极性和法伊，今年举办比赛在爱神1月12日在NBC
how great stories come to a tension thanks to our NBC station in Denver Kusa a 6 year old boy areas name Connor who wants to save NASA in this potion to Lyra and get them back in the business of launching American astronauts in space
多么伟大的故事来张力感谢我们的NBC电台在丹佛库萨一个6岁男孩的地区命名康纳谁愿意在这个药水保存美国宇航局莱拉，让他们回去发动美国宇航员在太空中的业务
show with the support of his daddy launched a campaign that got a petition on the White House website is receive letters
显示出与他爸爸的支持下推出了拿到了一份请愿书的白宫网站上的活动是收到信件
phone calls from people around the world including one particular call Walmart camera crew was there from a guy who speaks from experience
来自世界各地的人，包括一个特定的呼叫沃尔玛摄制组的电话是从那里谁从经验讲一个家伙
I am a national change the last person to walk on the moon
我是一个国家改变最后一个人在月球上行走
what how about that as in the Gene Cernan last man to walk on the moon when Im to say quote to go to the moon you got a dream about things that a lot of other people think you can't do
什么怎么样，由于在基因塞尔南最后一位在月球上行走时，林说帖去你得到的东西是梦想月亮，很多其他人认为你不能做
perhaps lost in all the uproar over the incompetent sign language interpreter at the Mandela memorial is the fact that deaf people are the ones who lost out at a long nose
也许是失去了所有的沸沸扬扬了不称职的手语翻译在曼德拉纪念的事实是，聋人是谁失去了在一个长鼻子的那些
lines video of a little girl performing in her kindergarten Christmas show in Florida has service
的表演在她的幼儿园圣诞表演在佛罗里达州一个小女孩行视频有服务
she's seen here signing so that her deaf parents in the audience follow along it's fantastic delivered with Augusto you would expect from a child at that
她看到这里签署，使她的聋哑父母在台下跟着它的神奇交付使用奥古斯托你会期望从一个孩子在那
Takeya ler great age when we come back here tonight making a difference with a very special delivery
竹谷LER伟大的时代，当我们回到这里，今晚发挥作用有一个非常特殊的交付
making a difference to buy new oxytrol for women
制造差异，以购买新oxytrol妇女
and finally tonight a woman who's been making a difference for America's military men and women for a decade she is just in fact mark the milestone with her own you
终于今晚一个女人谁是被制作为美国的军人和妇女了十年的差别，她只是在实际上标志着她自己你的里程碑
way of saying thanks we get the story tonight from our Pentagon correspondent Jim McClure Shefsky who went on quite a journey himself to bring us your story
为表示感谢的方式我们从五角大楼的记者吉姆·麦克卢尔Shefsky谁去不少自己的旅程带给我们您的故事得到了今晚的故事
the guided missile cruiser Gettysburg in the faraway Gulf of Oman holiday spirits were running sky high sailors way to get packages like Christmas morning
导弹巡洋舰在葛底斯堡的阿曼节日精神遥远的海湾正在运行天高水兵的方式来获得包像圣诞节的早晨
early from those long lonely deployments Etsy
从早期的那些漫长寂寞的部署Etsy的
the driving force behind the festivities Caroline black chick founder of operation gratitude
操作感恩庆祝活动卡罗琳黑鸡创始人的原动力
this is the end come true to get high from 360 sailors at sea nothing to be better
这是结束成真，以得到360水手在高海没有什么更好
venta de marca monumental milestone Operation Gratitude is 1 million
本塔 - 品牌不朽的里程碑操作感恩是100万
present a petty officer Brooke Hogan
提出了一个士官布鲁克霍根
that's a long way from 10 years ago packages one time
这是从10年前一个很长的路要走包一次
today and volunteer turns out 3008 California
今天和志愿者原来加州3008
Volunteers of all ages like 103 year old Eco in a veteran of World War 2
各年龄段喜欢103年老在生态二战老兵的志愿者
the most cherished gifts personal letters from Volunteers like Matthew
最珍爱的礼物像马修志愿者私人信件
did the settlers of the Gettysburg Address are more than just an early Christmas present their sign of Americas respect love and gratitude for their service
没有的葛底斯堡演说的定居者不仅仅是一个早期的圣诞节礼物美洲尊重的爱和感谢他们的服务他们的标志
officer Oakman got just a little more
奥克曼人员得到了一点点
keys to your own 2014 forever
键来自己的2014永远
Chuck E Cheese
查Ë奶酪
personal mission is far from over
个人的使命远未结束
she's already planning for a second Millions prize Jimmy akin DC news aboard the Gettysburg
她已经筹划登上葛底斯堡第二个百万大奖吉米类似于特区新闻
and that's our broadcast for this Thursday night thank you for being here with us I'm Brian Williams on way of course hope to see you right back here tomorrow is good
这就是我们的广播这个星期四晚上谢谢你能在这里和我们我布莱恩·威廉姆斯，当然这样希望看到你的右后卫在这里明天是好的